active-bookmarks.com 2012-11-28

# Privacy Policy | active bookmarks - Dofollow blogs - Dofollow site - Dofollow News - Dofollow Article - Dofollow Forums - Dofollow Video

  * Upcoming News
  * Submit a New Story
  * Groups

Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy  
policy, please feel free to contact us by email at  
[Contact Us](http://active-bookmarks.com/page.php?page=privacy-policy "Contact Us") .

At [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks"), the privacy of our  
visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines  
the types of personal information is received and collected by [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks") and how it is used.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks")  
makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes  
internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (  
ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze  
trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather  
demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked  
to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons

[active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks") does use cookies to store  
information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on  
which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on  
visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their  
browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks").

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based  
on their visit to [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks") and other  
sites on the Internet

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and  
content network privacy policy at the following URL - [   
http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/)  

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.  
Our advertising partners include ..

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the  
advertisements and links that appear on [active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks")  
send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when  
this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons )  
may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of  
their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you  
see.

[active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks") has no access to or  
control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad  
servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for  
instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  
[active-bookmarks.com](http://www.active-bookmarks.com/ "active bookmarks") privacy policy does not  
apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web  
sites.
